本字幕由高清电台整理发布，更多高清电影请访问
https://gaoqing.fm
Where's Jay?
How long were those potatoes under the fire? How'd you do that?
-Somebody will see! -No way.
-Does Maryann kiss as good as I do? -How would I know?
-You said we were special. -I meant everything.
-That's not allowed. -Come on.
Come on. A man is not made out of stone.
Somebody's there!
We weren't doing anything. We were just messing a--
Please, don't!
No!
Hi, girl. Excuse me! Hi, boy.
You speak English? How far is it to Camp Crystal Lake?
That far? Okey-dokey. See you later.
It's 7:01 on Friday the 13th of June.
This is Big Dave and it's time for you lazybones to get out of bed.
It's black-cat day in Crystal Lake.
I must have seen that Kojak 82 times.
Excuse me. How far is Camp Crystal Lake from here?
What is it, Enos? About 20 miles?
-About that. -Camp Blood?
-They're opening that place again? -Lots of luck.
-Can I get a bus or something? -Not likely.
You going out to the crossroads, Enos? What about a lift? That would be halfway.
No sweat, Trudy. Okay, kid, let's move it.
-Name's Annie. -All right, Annie, let's go.
All the girls up there gonna look as good as you?
I don't know.
-You're going to Camp Blood, ain't you? -Goddamn it, Ralph, get out of here!
-Leave people alone! -You'll never come back!
Oh, shut up, Ralph!
It's got a death curse!
He's a real prophet of doom, ain't he?
Climb up, miss.
He's causing problems enough for your boss with all that talk.
Goddamn nuisance.
-He tell you anything? -Who?
Your boss. Steve Christy.
I'll be cooking for 50 kids and 10 staff.
-Campers will mostly be inner-city children. -No, I mean about what happened.
No.
Come on. There's something you're not telling me.
-Quit. Quit now. -Quit? Why would I want to quit?
Camp Crystal Lake is jinxed!
Terrific. Not you too. You sound like your crazy friend back there.
Well, maybe. Did Christy tell you about the two kids murdered in '58?
Boy drowning in '57? A bunch of fires?
Nobody knows who did any of them.
In 1962, they were going to open up. The water was bad.
Christy will end up like his folks: Crazy and broke.
He's been up there a year fixing up that place. Must have dropped $25,000.
And for what? Ask anybody.
-Quit! -I can't.
Dumb kids. Know-it-alls.
Just like my nieces. Heads full of rocks.
-You're an American original. -I'm an American original.
-Dumb kid. -At least I'm not afraid of ghosts.
-Take care of yourself. -No sweat. Thanks for the lift.
Hey, Marcie. You really think there'll be other gorgeous women...
...at Camp Crystal Lake besides yourself?
-Is sex all you ever think about, Ned? -Hey, no. No. Absolutely not.
Sometimes I just think about kissing women.
-You wanna give me a hand over here? -Sure.
Alice! I wanna get this tree stump out.
Get on this side, you pull on that side. Alice!
Coming.
-That's great. I'm Steve Christy. -Jack.
-Marcie -Ned Rubinstein.
Welcome to Camp Crystal Lake. This is Alice.
Hi. Steve, Cabin B is all ready.
-Where's Bill? Cleaning out the boathouse? -Haven't seen him in half an hour.
I wanted him to start painting. Brenda?
-Setting up the archery range. -I'd rather she paint. Come on. Let's go.
I thought we had two weeks.
Come on. I'll show you where you can get changed.
-Here, let me give you a hand with that. -Thank you.
You got it?
You draw very well.
Thanks. I wish I had more time to do it.
Oh, dummy.
-When did you do this? -Last night.
-Do I really look like that? -You did last night.
You're very talented.
You're very pretty.
This really isn't your cup of tea, is it?
Any particular reason?
It's just a problem I have. It's nothing personal.
-You wanna leave? -I don't know. I may have to...
...go back to California to straighten something out.
Come on. Give me another chance.
Stay a week. Help get the place ready.
By Friday, if you're not happy, I'll put you on the bus myself.
All right. Friday. I'll give it a week.
Thanks, Alice.
Bill? Steve wants to know if we need more paint.
-Paint's all right. Need more thinner, though. -Okay.
-Alice. Did the others show up? -Yeah, everybody except that girl Annie.
-Think you're gonna last all summer? -I don't know if I'm gonna last all week.
-I'll tell Steve about the thinner. -Fine.
-You want it listed separately? -Right.
Brenda, I want you to finish the archery range.
If Annie gets here, get her started in the kitchen. Do your best.
I'll be back sometime after lunch.
It's supposed to rain like hell, so get as much done as possible.
He neglected to mention that downtown they call this place "Camp Blood."
Next there'll be snakes in the outhouse and crocodiles in the lake.
No, the crocodiles are in the cabins.
-Are you crazy? -Wanna see my trick shot? It's even better.
I don't believe you!
You know, you're beautiful when you're angry, sweetheart.
-Yeah? -Yeah.
You come to help me or scare me to death? You do that again...
-...l'll tack you up on the wall to dry. -I love that sexy talk!
Hi. I'm going to Camp Crystal Lake.
Guess I always wanted to work with children.
I hate when people call them "kids." Sounds like little goats.
But when you've had a dream as long as I have, you'll do anything.
Hey, wasn't that the road for Camp Crystal Lake back there?
I think we better stop.
Please?
Stop, please! Please! Stop!
Please, stop!
No. No.
No.
All right, move it out. A little to the left. Little to the left.
Move it out. Move it out. Okay, little to the left. Now-- No, no.
Let's go. Okay. Okay. Good. Good.
If you were a flavor of ice cream, what would it be?
-Rocky Road. -Hey!
What's that vitamin C stuff do for you, anyway?
Vitamin C is supposed to neutralize the nitrates or something.
What's the matter? Do you see something?
No. Nothing.
Ned! Get out of here!
-Hey, you guys. Ready to go back to work? -Yeah.
-Come on, Alice. -Help! Help!
-Something's wrong with Ned. -Get a life preserver!
-Can he swim? -I don't know.
-He's right around here somewhere. -I got it.
Go ahead, dive for him.
-There he is! -Come on. Help me.
Watch his head.
-Watch his head! -Got him?
-Can you give mouth-to-mouth? -Yeah.
-Oh, God. -Come on, Ned.
-Oh, Neddy! -Oh, Jesus Christ!
Look, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, all right?
Bill!
Bill, come here, quick! Hurry!
-What is it? -There's a snake over there.
Where?
-What do I do? -Kill it.
It might bite.
-Haven't you ever been in the woods? -We're not in the woods.
-Bill, what are you doing? -There's a snake.
-Why are we in here? -Feet don't fail me now!
-There it is! -Oh, God!
-I can't sleep with a snake in here. -Nobody said anything about snakes.
-Kill it! -I can't get it until it comes out.
-Well, call him! -How do you call a snake?
I'll flush him!
-I got it. -Where--?
-Look out! -I got him!
Oh, God.
Is it dead?
Either that or it's got a very short clone.
-Well, at least we know what's for dinner. -Marcie!
I'm making salad. Want me to make some for everybody?
-That would be great. There's hamburger-- -None for me.
There are apples. Know how to make apple pie?
-Sure. No sweat. -What is going on?
Oh, shit.
-Who are you people? -Camp counselors. Ned is just fooling around.
-Right, just-- -Can it, Cochise.
Steve Christy hire you people? He pay you for this?
-Nice bike. -You been smoking, boy?
Smoking? Don't smoke. Causes cancer.
You just get off a spaceship or something? Colombian gold. Grass. Hash. The weed.
-What's he talking about? -Don't get smart.
-Me? I'm as dumb as they come. -Not another word out of you, understand?
Nothing's going on here. We're getting the place in shape.
For what?
-Is there anything we can do to help? -I'm looking for somebody.
-Who's that? -A guy named Ralph. The town crazy.
There's no crazy people around here.
I told you to sit on it, Tonto. I got word Ralph was pedaling out this way...
-...spouting his gospel. -We haven't seen anybody here.
-Just us. -This guy Ralph. Is he dangerous?
Every time that loony gets drunk, he gets his calling.
I spend the morning in court, he gets a week in jail.
Cycle Two, where are you? Come in, Cycle Two.
This is Dorf. I'm out here at Camp Crystal Lake. Over.
Haul it back in, Dorf. Chief wants you back in town.
Roger that. 10-4. On my way. Out.
Never keep the chief waiting.
You kids keep your noses clean, understand? You'll be hearing from me if you don't.
We ain't gonna stand for no weirdness out here.
I'm a messenger of God. You're doomed if you stay here.
This place is cursed. Cursed.
-It's got a death curse! -Who are you?
What do you want?
-God sent me. -Get out of here, man!
I got to warn you. You're doomed if you stay.
Go. Go!
-I think we just met Ralph. -God, what's next?
You're doomed. You're all doomed.
-Who likes them rare? -Me.
How can you guys eat that? It looks like dead animals.
Dead animals? That's the old counselors. You cannibals!
If you would mix this stuff right, you'd get all the protein you need.
Too bad Annie never showed. She was supposed to be a good cook.
-Don't expect me to play chef. -The squaws are revolting.
-Trouble? -Yeah. A bad bulb or no power.
Seems a little gloomy in here.
Steve taught me how to use the emergency generator.
-Town power lines are lousy. -Don't you love that macho talk?
Emergency generator.
-Want to give me a hand? -Yeah.
-Wait for me. -Can you watch the burgers?
-Sure. -Burn them.
-Think he's gonna be bent out of shape? -I don't know.
This looks almost like the one at my uncle's cabin in Maine.
-Well, here goes. -What an antique.
Well, what hath God wrought?
Hello?
Can I help you?
Hello? Hello?
-Come on. -Coming, I'm coming.
Wind's come up. Shifted a good 180 degrees.
Makes me want to hold onto you.
-What about Ned? -I don't love Ned.
-He keeps acting like such a jerk. -Neddy!
-Don't call him. -Thought you wanted to give him...
...one of your motherly lectures.
Look, Neddy's gonna do whatever Neddy wants to do, you know?
It's gonna storm. Gonna tear down that valley like a son of a gun.
I've been afraid of storms since I was little.
No. Really?
I've had this dream about five or six times where I'm in a thunderstorm...
...and it's raining really hard. It sounds like pebbles when it hits the ground.
I hear it and I try to block it out with my hands, only it doesn't work.
It just keeps getting louder and louder.
And then the rain turns to blood...
...and the blood washes away in little rivers...
...and then the sound stops.
-It's just a dream. -I know. I call it my "shower dream."
Hey, hey. This is no dream. Come on, we're gonna get soaked.
Jack and Marcie are gonna get drenched!
Not if they're where I think they are.
That's nice.
I know what we can do. We'll play Monopoly.
-I hate Monopoly! -Not the way I play it, you don't.
-Like what? -We're going to play strip Monopoly.
-I'll be the shoe. -You have got to be kidding.
What if Steve walks in?
We'll give him a handicap. He can keep his boots on. It's easy.
Instead of rent, you pay clothes. Bill can be banker. Unless he's chicken.
Heaven help you if you land in my hotel!
Why don't you see if Marcie left any of that grass?
-What happened to my 500's? -They're there. Where's my shoe?
I'm not going to pass "Go" without a glow.
We rolled for you. You're going last.
Community Chest cannot give you your clothes back.
Double sixes! I get to roll again!
-We're being hustled. -I think you're right.
You are so fine.
Where are you going?
I gotta pee. You're lying on my bladder.
Hurry back, okay? It's getting cold in here.
-You'll save my place for me? -Yeah.
Five.
-Baltic Avenue. I'll buy it. -No one ever lands on Baltic Avenue.
I think it's a pretty color.
Come on.
Eight.
-Baltic Avenue. You owe me one boot. -Coming.
Alice draws first blood.
-That's a terrible way to talk about my feet. -Thank you.
Who's next?
You know I think I'm beginning to like this game.
Wait until he lands on my old Kentucky home.
-More beer? More beer. -Let's see. A railroad.
Forty Yards to the Outhouse, by Willie Makit.
Come on, kids, you can do better than that.
Jack?
When I looked into that mirror, I knew I'd always be ugly.
I said, "Lady, you'll always be plain."
Hello?
Ned?
Hey, come on, you guys.
It must be my imagination.
-Hello. -Shit.
Worst run of bad luck since Richard Nixon.
You can call it quits.
Fat chance! You're two steps from Pacific Avenue and Skin City.
What can I say? It's not much, but I call it home.
-I'll get it. I'll get it. -Get the money.
-God! -It's blowing like crazy out there.
I think I left the windows in my cabin open. Shoot!
We'll have to finish this game some other night.
Just when it was getting interesting.
-See you guys in the morning. -See you.
-Good night. -Good night.
Look at this mess! Here.
-Were you going to go ahead with it? -I hadn't made up my mind.
We'll have to finish the game another night.
-Is there anything else you want? -No, thanks, Sandy. I'm fine.
You can't go out in that rain. You want to drown?
I've got to. I've got six new counselors at camp.
They are babes in the woods, in every sense.
They'll be okay if they know enough to come out of the rain.
-Well, what do I owe you? -Just a night on the town, Steve.
-Come on now, you know what I mean. -That's okay. Two and a quarter.
Thank you.
-Here's your change. -No, you keep it.
-Thank you. -Sure.
-Drive careful. -I will.
Good night.
-Hi. -Hi.
-Thought that'd go through anything. -Not dragging a trailer.
Can you give me a lift?
-I'll have a counselor bring me back. -Why not?
Help me!
Hello.
-Hello. -Over here. Please somebody help me.
Hello?
Come quickly, please. Come quickly. Help.
Where are you? Hello.
Hello?
All right.
Come on out! You're not funny anymore!
It's not funny at all.
Bill.
-Hi. The generator is okay. -I thought I heard a scream.
-How can you hear in that wind? -It sounded like Brenda.
I'd better look.
Somebody turned on the lights at the archery range.
I can't see anything.
They're off now.
I'm gonna check it out.
-Bill. Can I come? -Come on.
Brenda!
Where is she?
She must be with Jack and Marcie.
-Alice? -Yeah?
Come here.
What is going on?
Come on!
-Jack, open the door. -Jack.
-Where are they? -I don't know. Come on.
Brenda?
Marcie?
Jack? Neddy?
Bill, I think we should call someone.
If this is a joke, I'll brain them!
I'm serious. I really think we should call someone.
The sucker's locked.
-Where's the key? -I don't know.
Wait a minute.
Watch out.
Be careful.
Let me get the light.
What's wrong?
It's dead. Try the pay phone.
Do you have a dime or a quarter?
No. Check the desk.
Hello?
This damn thing's dead too!
What's the matter with it?
It's wet.
I don't know.
Why don't we just hike out of here? Get out. Right now!
It's 10 miles to the nearest crossroads. Steve will be back soon.
We can use his jeep if we need to get help. Don't worry.
-There's some stupid explanation for this. -Like what?
We'll be laughing about this tomorrow, I promise.
Let's get out of the rain.
It's not bad enough to have Friday the 13th, we've gotta have a full moon too.
We keep statistics. We have more accidents, more rapes, more robberies...
...more homicides, more of everything when there's a full moon.
It upsets people. Makes them nuts.
You're making science out of coincidence.
I hear Ralph was out your way today.
His wife was a nervous wreck until we got him home.
That's all I need, Crazy Ralph running around.
Well, the rain's stopping.
It was a pisser while it lasted.
Sgt. Tierney, come in. Sgt. Tierney, Car Niner.
This is Tierney.
Rescue squad with Jaws of Life. Near mile-marker 17. Possible fatals.
Three, maybe more, trapped. Head on.
Roger. Acknowledge receipt. Estimate arrival, 15 minutes.
-I have to let you off here. -Sure.
Thanks.
Good luck.
Who is that?
What are you doing out in this mess?
What do you think happened?
I don't know.
The generator's probably out of gas.
I'll go check it.
Do you want me to come with you?
Why don't you stay here and try and sleep.
I'll be right back.
Full of gas.
Generator.
What am I gonna do?
Please! Oh, please!
Who are you?
I'm Mrs. Voorhees. An old friend of the Christys.
No, no. There, there.
I can't help you if you don't calm down.
But she's dead and he's dead. Oh, my God! Poor Bill! Oh, God!
-All right. Come on, dear. Show me. -No. No!
It's all right. I'll take care of you. I used to work for the Christys.
What's going on? Help me get out of here!
It's this place and the storm. That's why you're upset.
No, no! They're all dead! They're all dead!
-All right. I'll go look. -Don't leave me!
They'll kill you too!
I'm not afraid.
Oh, my Lord!
So young.
So pretty.
What monster could have done this?
Bill is out there!
Oh, God, this place!
Steve should never have opened this place again!
There's been too much trouble here.
Did you know a young boy drowned?
The year before those two others were killed.
The counselors weren't paying attention!
They were making love while that young boy drowned!
His name was Jason.
I was working the day it happened. Preparing meals.
Here. I was the cook.
Jason should have been watched! Every minute!
He was--
He wasn't a very good swimmer.
We can go now, dear.
I think we should wait for Mr. Christy.
That's not necessary.
I don't understand.
Help me!
Help!
Help, Mommy!
Help! Help, Mommy!
I am, Jason.
I am.
You see, Jason was my son.
And today is his birthday.
Where's Mr. Christy?
I couldn't let them open this place again.
Could I?
Not after what happened.
Oh, my sweet, innocent Jason.
My only child.
Jason.
You let him drown!
You never paid any attention!
Look what you did to him!
Kill her, Mommy. Kill her!
Don't let her get away, Mommy. Don't let her live!
I won't, Jason. I won't!
Where are the goddamn bullets?
Come, dear.
It will be easier for you than it was for Jason.
Kill her, Mommy. Kill her!
Kill her.
Kill her, Mommy. Kill her.
She can't hide. No place to hide.
Get her, Mommy. Get her!
Kill her! Kill her.
Get off me!
Ten milligrams, Valium. It's all right.
It's all over. Everything's over.
Roll over. Roll over, dear.
Your folks are on the way up.
Is anyone else alive?
Are they all dead?
Yes, ma'am.
Two of my men pulled you out of the lake. We thought you were dead too.
Do you remember very much?
The boy.
Is he dead too?
-Who? -The boy, Jason.
Jason?
In the lake. The one who attacked me. The one who pulled me under the water.
Ma'am, we didn't find any boy.
But he....
Then he's still there.
杰伊呢？
那些土豆在火下烧了多长时间？ 你是怎么做到的？
-有人会看到的！ -不可能。
-玛丽安吻得和我一样好吗？ -我怎么知道？
-你说我们很特别。 -我是认真的。
-这是不允许的。 -来吧。
来吧。人不是石头造的。
有人在那里！
我们什么也没做。 我们只是在捣乱--
求你了，不要！
不！
嗨，女孩。请原谅我！嗨，孩子。
你说英语？ 到水晶湖营地有多远？
那么远？ 好的，多基。再见。
今天是6月13日星期五7:01。
这是大戴夫，该你了 懒汉起床。
今天是水晶湖的黑猫日。
我一定看过82遍了。
请原谅我。有多远 水晶湖营地在这里吗？
怎么了，伊诺斯？大约20英里？
-关于这个。 -营血？
-他们又在开那个地方？ -祝你好运。
-我能坐公共汽车吗？ -不太可能。
你要去十字路口吗，伊诺斯？ 搭便车怎么样？那就一半了。
别出汗，特鲁迪。好了，孩子，我们走吧。
-我叫安妮。 -好吧，安妮，我们走。
上面所有的女孩 会和你一样好看吗？
我不知道。
-你要去扎营，不是吗？ -该死的，拉尔夫，滚出去！
-别管别人！ -你再也回不来了！
哦，闭嘴，拉尔夫！
它有一个死亡诅咒！
他真是个预言家，不是吗？
爬上去，小姐。
他引起的麻烦已经够多了 为了你的老板。
他妈的讨厌。
-他跟你说了什么？ -谁？
你的老板。史蒂夫?克里斯蒂。
我要为50个孩子和10个员工做饭。
-露营者大多是市中心的孩子。 -不，我是说发生了什么。
不。
来吧。有件事 你没告诉我。
-退出。现在退出。 -退出？我为什么要辞职？
水晶湖营地真倒霉！
极好的。你也不是。你听起来 就像你那疯狂的朋友。
嗯，也许吧。克莉丝蒂有没有告诉你 那两个孩子在58年被谋杀了？
57年溺水的男孩？一堆火？
没人知道是谁干的。
1962年，他们打算开放。 水不好。
克里斯蒂最终会像他的家人一样： 疯了，破产了。
他在那里修了一年了 地点。肯定掉了25000美元。
为了什么？问问任何人。
-别说了！ -我不能。
傻孩子。无所不知。
就像我的侄女一样。满是石头的脑袋。
-你是美国原创。 -我是美国原创的。
-傻孩子。 -至少我不怕鬼。
-照顾好你自己。 -不流汗。谢谢你的搭车。
嘿，玛西。你真的认为 会有其他漂亮的女人。。。
…在水晶湖营地除了你自己？
-你只想过性吗，内德？ -嘿，不。不。绝对不是。
有时候我只想着亲吻女人。
-你想帮我一下吗？ -当然。
爱丽丝！我想把这个树桩拿出来。
站在这边，你拉 在那边。爱丽丝！
来了。
-太好了。我是史蒂夫?克里斯蒂。 -杰克。
-玛西 -内德?鲁宾斯坦。
欢迎来到水晶湖营地。 我是爱丽丝。
你好。史蒂夫，B舱准备好了。
-比尔呢？清理船屋？ -半小时没见他了。
我想让他开始画画。布伦达？
-建立射箭场。 -我宁愿她画画。来吧。走吧。
我以为我们有两个星期。
来吧。我给你看 换衣服的地方。
-来，让我帮你一把。 -谢谢你。
你明白了吗？
你画得很好。
谢谢。我希望我有更多的时间去做。
哦，笨蛋。
-你什么时候做的？ -昨晚。
-我真的像那样吗？ -你昨晚做的。
你很有天赋。
你真漂亮。
这真的不是你的茶，是吗？
有什么特别的原因吗？
我只是有个问题。 这不是私人问题。
-你想离开吗？ -我不知道。我可能不得不。。。
…回加州去 把事情弄清楚。
来吧。再给我一次机会。
呆一周。 帮我把地方准备好。
到星期五，如果你不高兴， 我自己送你上车。
好吧。星期五。我给你一个星期。
谢谢，爱丽丝。
账单？史蒂夫想知道 如果我们需要更多的油漆。
-油漆没问题。不过，需要更薄一点。 -好吧。
-爱丽丝。其他人出现了吗？ -是啊，除了那个女孩安妮。
-你以为你能撑整个夏天？ -我不知道我是否能坚持一周。
-我会告诉史蒂夫关于稀释剂的事。 -很好。
-你想单列吗？ -是的。
布伦达，我要你 完成射箭射程。
如果安妮来了，让她开始 在厨房里。尽力而为。
午饭后我会回来的。
天要下地狱般的雨， 所以尽可能多的做。
他没提到市中心 他们把这个地方叫做“营血”
接下来会有蛇在 外屋和湖里的鳄鱼。
不，鳄鱼在小屋里。
-你疯了吗？ -想看我的特技镜头吗？更好了。
我不相信你！
你知道，你很漂亮 当你生气的时候，亲爱的。
-是吗？ -是的。
你来帮我还是吓唬我 我死定了？你再来一次。。。
-……我把你钉在墙上晾干。 -我喜欢那性感的谈话！
你好。我要去水晶湖露营。
我想我一直都想 和孩子们一起工作。
我讨厌别人叫他们“孩子” 听起来像小山羊。
但当你做了一个梦 只要我有，你什么都可以做。
嘿，这不是路吗 后面的水晶湖营地？
我想我们最好停下来。
拜托？
请停下！拜托！住手！
拜托，住手！
不，不。
不。
好吧，把它搬出去。往左一点。 向左一点。
把它搬出去。把它搬出去。可以， 向左一点。现在——不，不。
走吧。可以。可以。很好。很好。
如果你是冰淇淋的味道， 会是什么？
-洛基路。 -嘿！
维生素C是什么 不管怎样，这些东西对你有用吗？
维生素C应该能中和 硝酸盐什么的。
怎么了？你看到什么了吗？
不，没什么。
奈德！离开这里！
-嘿，你们两个。准备好回去工作了吗？ -是的。
-来吧，爱丽丝。 -救命啊！救命啊！
-内德有点不对劲。 -找个救生圈！
-他会游泳吗？ -我不知道。
-他就在这附近的某个地方。 -我明白了。
去吧，为他潜水。
-他来了！ -来吧。帮助我。
小心他的头。
-小心他的头！ -找到他了吗？
-你能嘴对嘴吗？ -是的。
-哦，天哪。 -来吧，内德。
-哦，内迪！ -哦，天哪！
听着，对不起。对不起，好吗？
账单！
比尔，过来，快！快点！
-这是什么？ -那边有条蛇。
在哪里？
-我该怎么办？ -杀了它。
可能会咬人。
-你没去过树林吗？ -我们不在树林里。
-比尔，你在干什么？ -有条蛇。
-我们为什么在这里？ -别让我失望！
-就在那儿！ -哦，天哪！
-我不能和蛇一起睡在这里。 -没人提起蛇。
-杀了它！ -它出来之前我拿不到。
-好吧，打电话给他！ -你怎么叫蛇？
我来冲他！
-我明白了。 -哪里？
-当心！ -我抓住他了！
哦，天哪。
它死了吗？
要么是这个，要么是一个很短的克隆。
-好吧，至少我们知道晚饭吃什么。 -玛西！
我在做沙拉。想要我 给大家做点？
-那太好了。有汉堡包-- -我没有。
有苹果。 知道怎么做苹果派吗？
-当然。不流汗。 -怎么回事？
哦，妈的。
-你们是谁？ -营地顾问。内德只是在胡闹。
-对，只是-- -可以吗，可可丝。
史蒂夫?克里斯蒂雇你们？ 他付钱给你？
-不错的自行车。 -你一直在抽烟，孩子？
吸烟？别抽烟。导致癌症。
你刚从飞船上下来什么的？ 哥伦比亚黄金。草。搞砸。杂草。
-他在说什么？ -别那么聪明。
-我？我和他们一样笨。 -别再说了，明白吗？
这里什么都没发生。 我们要把这个地方修好。
为了什么？
-我们能帮上什么忙吗？ -我在找人。
-那是谁？ -一个叫拉尔夫的人。小镇疯了。
这里没有疯子。
我叫你坐在上面，托托。我有消息 拉尔夫正骑着自行车往这边走。。。
-…宣讲他的福音。 -我们在这里没见过任何人。
-只有我们。 -这家伙拉尔夫。他危险吗？
每次那个疯子喝醉， 他接到电话了。
字幕译制--贝支子--
我在法庭上呆了一上午， 他坐牢一周。
第二轮，你在哪里？ 进来，第二轮。
我是多夫。我在外面 在水晶湖营地。结束。
把它拉回来，多夫。 头儿要你回镇上。
收到。10-4岁。已经上路了。出去。
别让头儿等着。
你们两个保持鼻子干净，明白吗？ 如果你不告诉我你会收到我的信的。
我们不会站着的 别怪我。
我是上帝的使者。 如果你呆在这里，你就完了。
这个地方被诅咒了。诅咒。
-它有一个死亡诅咒！ -你是谁？
你想要什么？
-上帝派我来的。 -滚开，伙计！
我得警告你。 如果你留下来，你就完了。
去吧。快走！
-我想我们刚认识拉尔夫。 -天哪，接下来呢？
你命中注定。你们都注定了。
-谁喜欢稀有的？ -我。
你们怎么能吃那个？ 看起来像死了的动物。
死去的动物？那是老顾问。 你们这些食人族！
如果你能把这些东西混合好， 你会得到你需要的所有蛋白质。
可惜安妮没露面。 她应该是个好厨师。
-别指望我当厨师。 -刑警正在反抗。
-麻烦？ -是的。灯泡坏或没电。
这里看起来有点阴郁。
史蒂夫教我如何使用 应急发电机。
-镇上的电力线很糟糕。 -你不喜欢那种男子汉的谈话吗？
应急发电机。
-想帮我一把吗？ -是的。
-等我。 -你能看汉堡吗？
-当然。 -烧掉它们。
-你觉得他会变形吗？ -我不知道。
这个看起来和那个差不多 在缅因州我叔叔的小屋里。
-好吧，给你。 -多古董啊。
上帝做了什么？
你好？
我能帮助你吗？
你好？你好？
-来吧。 -来了，我来了。
风来了。 移动了180度。
让我想抓住你。
-奈德呢？ -我不爱内德。
-他一直表现得像个混蛋。 -内迪！
-别打电话给他。 -以为你想给他。。。
……你的一个母亲般的演讲。
听着，内迪会做任何事的 内迪想这么做，你知道吗？
会有暴风雨的。要拆了 那个山谷就像一把枪的儿子。
我一直害怕暴风雨 从我小时候起。
不，真的吗？
我做了个五六岁的梦 当我遇到雷雨的时候。。。
……雨下得真大。听起来 就像石头砸在地上一样。
我听到了，我试着阻止它 用我的手，只是不管用。
它一直在变 越来越大声。
然后雨变成了血。。。
…血液会被冲走 在小河里。。。
…然后声音就停止了。
-只是个梦。 -我知道。我称之为我的“淋浴梦”
嘿，嘿。这不是梦。 快点，我们要湿透了。
杰克和玛西会湿透的！
如果他们在我想的地方就不会了。
很好。
我知道我们能做什么。 我们要玩垄断游戏。
-我讨厌垄断！ -不是我弹的，你不是。
-比如什么？ -我们要玩脱衣舞专卖。
-我会成为你的鞋。 -你一定是在开玩笑。
如果史蒂夫进来怎么办？
我们会给他一个障碍。 他能穿上靴子。很容易。
你付的不是房租，而是衣服。比尔 可以是银行家。除非他是胆小鬼。
如果你着陆了，上天会帮助你的 在我的酒店！
你为什么不看看玛西 留下草了吗？
-我500岁的时候怎么了？ -他们在那里。我的鞋呢？
我不会通过“去” 没有光芒。
我们为你翻身。你走到最后。
公益金不能 把衣服还给你。
双六！我又开始打滚了！
-我们被催促了。 -我认为你是对的。
你真好。
你要去哪里？
我要尿尿。 你躺在我的膀胱上。
快点回来，好吗？ 这里越来越冷了。
-你会为我保留我的位置吗？ -是的。
五个。
-波罗的海大道。我会买的。 -从来没有人在波罗的海大道着陆。
我觉得它的颜色很漂亮。
来吧。
八个。
-波罗的海大道。你欠我一只靴子。 -来了。
爱丽丝先抽血。
-那是谈论我脚的可怕方式。 -谢谢你。
下一个是谁？
你知道我觉得我开始 喜欢这个游戏。
等到他着陆 在我的肯塔基老家。
-再来点啤酒？再来点啤酒。 -让我们看看。铁路。
离外屋四十码， 作者：威利?马基特。
来吧，孩子们， 你可以做得更好。
杰克？
当我照镜子的时候， 我知道我总是很丑。
我说， “小姐，你永远都会很直白的。”
你好？
内德？
嘿，来吧，伙计们。
一定是我的想象。
-你好。 -妈的。
最坏的运气 自从理查德?尼克松。
你可以放弃。
机会不大！你走了两步 来自太平洋大道和皮肤城。
我能说什么？ 不多，但我称之为家。
-我去拿。我去拿。 -拿到钱。
-上帝啊！ -外面的风吹得很疯狂。
我想我离开了窗户 在我的小屋里。开枪！
我们必须完成这场比赛 改天晚上。
就在它变得有趣的时候。
-早上见。 -再见。
-晚安。 -晚安。
看看这一团糟！在这里。
-你打算继续吗？ -我还没有下定决心。
我们必须完成 又一个晚上的比赛。
-你还想要什么吗？ -不，谢谢，桑迪。我很好。
你不能在那样的雨中出去。 你想淹死吗？
我必须这么做。 我在营地有六个新的顾问。
他们是树林里的宝贝， 在任何意义上。
如果他们知道的够多就没事了 从雨中出来。
-我欠你什么？ -就在镇上待一晚，史蒂夫。
-来吧，你知道我的意思。 -没关系。两个四分之一。
谢谢您。
-这是找你的零钱。 -不，你留着。
-谢谢你。 -当然。
-小心驾驶。 -我会的。
晚安。
-嗨。 -嗨。
-我以为会经历任何事情。 -不拖拖车。
你能载我一程吗？
-我会让一个顾问带我回来。 -为什么不呢？
帮助我！
你好。
-你好。 -在这里。请有人帮帮我。
你好？
请快点来。 快点来。救命啊。
你在哪里？你好。
你好？
好吧。
快出来！你不再有趣了！
一点也不好笑。
账单。
-嗨。发电机没问题。 -我好像听到尖叫声。
-你怎么能听到风的声音？ -听起来像布伦达。
我最好看看。
有人把灯打开了 在射箭场。
我什么也看不见。
他们现在走了。
我去看看。
-比尔。我能来吗？ -来吧。
布伦达！
她在哪里？
她一定和杰克和玛西在一起。
-爱丽丝？ -是吗？
过来。
怎么回事？
快点！
-杰克，开门。 -杰克。
-他们在哪里？ -我不知道。来吧。
布伦达？
玛西？
杰克？内迪？
比尔，我想我们应该找个人。
如果这是一个笑话，我会让他们知道的！
我是认真的。 我真的认为我们应该找个人。
那混蛋被锁了。
-钥匙在哪里？ -我不知道。
等一下。
小心。
让我开灯。
发生了什么？
它死了。试试公用电话。
你有一角硬币还是四分之一？
不，查一下桌子。
你好？
这该死的东西也死了！
怎么了？
是湿的。
我不知道。
我们何不徒步离开这里？ 走出。马上！
离最近的十字路口有10英里。 史蒂夫很快就会回来。
如果需要我们可以用他的吉普车 去寻求帮助。别担心。
-有一些愚蠢的解释。 -比如什么？
明天我们会为此欢笑， 我保证。
让我们避雨吧。
13号星期五还不够糟， 我们也得有一个满月。
我们保留统计数据。我们有更多的事故， 更多的强奸，更多的抢劫。。。
…更多的凶杀案，更多的一切 当有满月的时候。
这让人不安。让他们发疯。
你在搞科学 出于巧合。
我听说拉尔夫今天不在你身边。
他的妻子神经衰弱 直到我们把他带回家。
这就是我所需要的， 疯狂的拉尔夫跑来跑去。
好吧，雨停了。
这是一个尿，而它持续。
蒂尔尼中士，进来。 蒂尔尼中士，九号车厢。
我是蒂尔尼。
带着生命之嘴的救援队。 接近英里标记17。可能的死亡。
三个，也许更多，被困。 迎面而来。
罗杰。确认收到。 预计15分钟到达。
-我得让你在这里下车。 -当然。
谢谢。
祝你好运。
那是谁？
你在做什么 在这混乱中？
你觉得发生了什么事？
我不知道。
发电机可能没油了。
我去看看。
你想让我和你一起去吗？
你为什么不留在这里 试着睡一觉。
我马上回来。
充满了气体。
发电机。
我该怎么办？
拜托！哦，求你了！
你是谁？
我是沃希斯太太。 基督的老朋友。
不，不。那里，那里。
我帮不了你 如果你不冷静下来。
但她死了他也死了。 哦，天哪！可怜的比尔！哦，天哪！
-好吧。来吧，亲爱的。向我展示。 -不，不！
没关系。我会照顾你的。 我以前为圣诞节工作。
发生什么事？ 帮我离开这里！
是这个地方和风暴。 这就是你生气的原因。
不，不！他们都死了！ 他们都死了！
-好吧。我去看看。 -别离开我！
他们也会杀了你！
我不怕。
哦，上帝！
太年轻了。
真漂亮。
是什么怪物干的？
比尔在外面！
哦，天哪，这地方！
史蒂夫不应该 又打开了这个地方！
这里太麻烦了。
你知道一个小男孩淹死了吗？
前一年那两个 被杀了。
顾问们没注意！
他们在做爱 当那个小男孩淹死的时候！
他叫杰森。
事情发生那天我正在工作。 准备饭菜。
在这里。我是厨师。
杰森应该被监视的！ 每一分钟！
他是--
他游泳游得不太好。
我们现在可以走了，亲爱的。
我想我们应该等克里斯蒂先生。
那没必要。
我不明白。
帮助我！
救命啊！
救命，妈妈！
救命啊！救命，妈妈！
我是，杰森。
我是。
你看，杰森是我儿子。
今天是他的生日。
克里斯蒂先生在哪里？
我不能让他们再打开这个地方。
我可以吗？
不是在发生了什么事之后。
哦，我亲爱的，无辜的杰森。
我唯一的孩子。
杰森。
你让他淹死了！
你从来没注意过！
看看你对他做了什么！
杀了她，妈妈。杀了她！
妈妈，别让她跑了。 别让她活着！
我不会的，杰森。我不会的！
该死的子弹呢？
来吧，亲爱的。
对你来说会更容易 而不是杰森。
杀了她，妈妈。杀了她！
杀了她。
杀了她，妈妈。杀了她。
她藏不住。 无处藏身。
抓住她，妈妈。抓住她！
杀了她！杀了她。
放开我！
10毫克，安定。 没关系。
一切都结束了。一切都结束了。
翻滚。滚过去，亲爱的。
你的家人正在赶来的路上。
还有人活着吗？
他们都死了吗？
是的，女士。
我的两个手下把你从湖里救了出来。 我们以为你也死了。
你还记得很多吗？
那个男孩。
他也死了吗？
-谁？ -那个男孩，杰森。
杰森？
在湖里。袭击我的那个人。 把我拉下水的那个人。
女士，我们没有找到男孩。
但他。。。。
那他还在那儿。